Viewers all over the world, I want to say thank you.
I salute your faith.
SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
I really want to be one of you today
so the message I have for you, I will read it page by page
so that you can be able to write it down.
Thank you.
Let me first of all say "thanks" to the following organisations and their support.
First, the state we are today – Lagos State and the Federal Government of Nigeria.
Thank you very much for your support and your prayer.
And the security agencies of different bodies -
I will not be able to mention you one by one, we have many security agencies around.
I want to salute you and thank you very much for your love and your prayer, and your support.
Let me also remember engineers and humanitarian groups with their equipment.
For some days now, I want to say thank you once again for your support.
Rescuers from different bodies – you just see people from everywhere.
Let me remember the doctors – what a wonderful people from all over... ,
not even Nigeria alone, but from everywhere and their hospitals too.
Media – I want to say "thank you" to the media
because I know the relationship of Jesus Christ with the media in the Bible.
Yes. Emmanuel TV is the media of Synagogue.
If we fight the media, we are fighting Emmanuel TV.
So, we want to salute you. Thank you very much.
Members and partners all over the world,
a big thanks! I am giving you a hug! Thank you for your prayer and love.
Neighbours, thank you very much for your support and your prayer.
Clergy and Christians all over the world – I want to say a very big thanks, and I salute your faith.
Let me remember diplomatic missions all over the world.
We received letters from nearly all the embassies, praying and supporting us in prayer
and asking what they can do.
I want to say thank you diplomatic missions all the world - thank you very much.
I want to use this opportunity to thank you.
There are many organizations I will not be able to mention.
If there is any organization I have not mentioned here,
I want to say thank you for your prayer and your love.
I want to start my message here.
I will just give you a detail because the security agencies need to do their job.
In a nutshell, let me start from the very day - that was Friday morning.
I was in the mountain.
I left there at exactly 8am in the morning and I received a phone call immediately.
After receiving a phone call, I immediately got here.
It was just a ten minutes interval.
When I was in the church, there was a jet hovering,
moving around at a very close range at the mountain which I had just left.
The place I left at the mountain, I received a phone call that there is a jet moving around that spot.
Well, I told them that I was in the church.
Before I knew it, I received a phone call again that there was a jet here,
the same jet here,
at the church, hovering around a building,
passing over the building four times at a very low range, before the building collapsed.
So, we are going to show you the video because the CCTV covered it.
OK, let's watch before I continue.
September 12, 2014. A building at the SCOAN collapses after a strange aircraft flies low,
multiple times over it before disappearing.
SCOAN visitors captured the strange aircraft on their camera at the entrance of the building.
A SCOAN visitor's photo – a strange aircraft flies low over a building at the SCOAN.
This is an enlarged view of the photograph taken.
It reveals the close proximity at which the strange aircraft flew over the building shortly before its collapse.
Let us listen to the visitors who took the photo, saw the aircraft and survived – September 12, 2014.
My name is Shadrack Mamzini. I am from South Africa.
We arrived here in September 11, 2014.
After the service in the main church, we went out for lunch.
When I was entering the other part of the church,
I wanted to take some pictures of the SCOAN buildings.
I took two pictures.
While I was taking the last picture, I discovered a very big aircraft.
It was something which was unusual in the way it looked.
It did not look like a passenger flight or an ordinary flight.
I asked myself what it was.
I thought maybe it was because the airport was close and the aircraft was going to land.
My worry was that it was too low to the building.
In South Africa, that kind of plane, such big aircrafts, don’t fly close to buildings.
I thought to myself that because the airport is close, the aircraft was trying to go and land.
There was a certain lady, who came into the canteen shouting and screaming,
crying that the building had collapsed.
It was when we went outside to see that, we saw it had collapsed.
I zoomed the picture where I saw the aircraft clearly on the picture.
This is a photograph taken by Mr Shadrack on his cell phone.
A look at the upper left-hand corner reveals the strange aircraft as it flew over the building.
By the time the incident happened, there were a lot of talks on it, that maybe the structure was poor.
Some said that the engineers were this and that.
It was until the man of God revealed what really happened,
I went back to check my photos, all the photos I had taken.
My name is Thobile Bhaku. I'm coming from South Africa.
When I entered the building, I heard the aircraft but I did not care about the aircraft.
I went inside the dining hall because it was lunch time.
On the queue, I was served.
While I was preparing coffee for myself, I heard a big sound behind me.
It was something like a big bang.
When I looked up, I saw the slab falling down.
Because of my experiences – I am a health and safety officer -
I have been trained on what to do.
When a beam is falling on top of you, you have to go opposite direction.
I ran to the opposite direction.
As I was running to the opposite direction, I saw the walls were cracking all over.
Suddenly, I was on the floor and it was dark, as if it was not during the day.
It was very, very hot and dark on the inside.
But in some cases, we could feel that there was fresh air coming in.
We did not know were the fresh air was coming from.
We prayed to God and thanked God.
We thank Prophet T.B. Joshua for praying for us.
All of us there, we are alive.
My name is Mick Milambo. I am from South Africa.
Originally from the Democratic Republic of the Congo.
I was walking with my friend, Joseph.
He is not here; he went back to South Africa today.
At the time, we walked and had just crossed the gate here.
We saw the aircraft.
It was just passing here, slowly – a big aircraft.
My friend told me, "If you see an aircraft like this, it is trouble".
The sound was not that big; it was small and it was a big aircraft.
But it was passing, not far but slowly.
After that, we went into the same building the aircraft had passed over.
That was the same building we were going to.
Our lunch was supposed to be taken there.
After that, they started serving lunch.
We managed to get our lunch.
I can say about after ten minutes, I heard just a sound.
You know, it was like glass, when you break glass.
We were just here; the wall was behind us.
We just turned to look at what had happened and we saw this thing was coming to us, fast.
It was very fast.
That was the sound.
Everyone was down.
We started calling each other.
Amazingly, everyone was alive.
We communicated with everyone.
We started praying.
God is great; we didn’t cease to shout the name of Jesus down there.
Emmanuel!
(God with us – Matthew 1:23)
Here speaks Charles Thawane from Johannesburg, South Africa.
On Friday, we were in the church.
At lunch time, we went out and were moving to where they were serving.
Where we were going was next to the building that later fell.
I saw the aircraft was going to the building
but I was with my friend and he was just taking photos of the SCOAN buildings.
That aircraft, when it came, I did not think it would come to the building
because it was coming as if it was going to pass the building
but suddenly when we saw it on the photo, it was turning to the building.
It was big.
It was big but it was not having sound too much.
The sound was not too much because if it was too much, I think everybody was going to look up.
It was a silent one when it was moving.
It was moving very slowly.
It looked like a jet.
It didn’t look like an ordinary plane that you take when you go somewhere.
After that, we passed the building.
We were going to where we were going to eat.
Then, my friend was still taking those photos.
That was what I had seen and then, that was it.
What I would like to confirm is what people saw on Emmanuel TV, the clip the man of God showed.
Some say it looks like a bird; it is not an aircraft.
But I would like to confirm it, that it was an aircraft.
We saw it; we witnessed it.
We thank God because on one of the pictures taken, the aircraft was captured.
I would like to believe it was the plan of God that pushed that excitement to take those pictures.
It was the Holy Spirit. Thank you very much.
Security footage September 12, 2014.
A strange aircraft flies low over a building at The SCOAN multiple times before the incident
and after the incident, the strange aircraft does not return.
September 12, 2014
Take note of the upper left-hand corner of the screen.
A strange aircraft flies over the building of The SCOAN before the incident at 11:30am.
Thirteen minutes later, the strange aircraft flies low over the building before the incident - 11:43am.
Just two minutes later, the strange aircraft returns and flies lower over the buildings
before the incident - 11:45am.
Nine minutes later, the strange aircraft returns and again flies low over the building
before the incident - 11:54am.
This is the moment of the incident.
After the incident, the strange aircraft does not return.
OK, thank you.
Let me continue my message.
After the fourth time, we could not see the aircraft again.
Let me read a little message for you before I bring out some details.
In this environment of Ikotun-Egbe, we have never witnessed an accident of a building collapse.
This is to tell you that we have a stable terrain in Ikotun-Egbe.
I have been in this community for the past 30 years
and there has been no record of a building collapse.
As a minister of the Gospel, our first priority is life saving.
There is no compromise in what we do at all.
I am going to leave this for you to judge.
Take note of that – I am pregnant of the word.
We have left the security to do their job.
Let us believe - take note of that - and educate our people and be alert.
Why we should believe -
so that our country will not witness a similar incident in another place.
This is not the first time.
If we believe, we will educate our people and be alert.
No matter how long a lie is sustained, the truth will some day prevail.
We should remember the militant who came with his group to this church with a bomb and he was arrested.
It was televised. Upon televising it and showing it on the screen,
all groups were saying it was a lie -
but later they discovered that it was true
because they felt their presence somewhere.
The case of the militant is still with the security.
The press men, the news all over the world said the story was false.
I know you will ask me, “Why Synagogue?”
That is the question that is going through you, “Why this church?”
Yes. Don’t forget the spiritual blessing that God has bestowed on us.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
A big head wears a large hat.
Don’t forget the ebola issue.
It was God who rescued this ministry from the issue.
They want to put the issue of ebola.
If possible, they would have taken an ebola patient and dropped it into the church.
You remember the text message you received: "Ebola is in the church - don't go there".
Cook hot water, put salt. Say: "T.B. Joshua".
You have forgotten? Don't forget.
God rescued this ministry from that.
They were trying to scare you from coming to this church.
Don’t be scared – you are not the target; I am the target.
I know my hour has not yet come.
Take note of that.
Don’t be scared – you are not the target; I am the target
and my hour has not yet come.
I have not yet finished my job.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I have not finished my job.
Anything close to Jesus receives attack.
Don’t forget the message you have been receiving for the past two weeks.
I was talking to you in parables.
Go over the messages – you will see the picture.
When a situation like this comes, you should know how to handle it.
It has come and God is on top of the matter.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Let me remind you of what I said during last Sunday service:
that what would be happening between now would be much much greater than 10 years.
How many of you were in the service?
I want to assure you that our God will get back to them.
Listen to me.
God will get back to them – the agents of satan, and you will know when He gets back to them.
You will know.
And I'm happy that the whole thing starts here.
I will tell you the reason why I say, "The whole thing starts here".
From the beginning, it has been a battle.
If you notice, I have been talking to you for the past two weeks in parables.
I want to show you some documents here.
These documents - I think my wife just sees them now for the first time.
Only those who received it from the email department and I.
Those who received those documents, I warned them: between me and you and God.
Nobody should see these documents.
But because of what has happened, I think - I will just show you one.
Just one.
I want somebody to come out and read this document.
With the picture.
"Man of God - my name is Emmanuel Anaja. I am from Kogi state, living in Jos,
right now with my parent, who is a soldier.
I have a confession to make.
I want to give my life to Jesus Christ, our Saviour.
I am a Boko Haram member.
I came to The SCOAN to plant a bomb in the Synagogue Church Of All Nations,
but I could not do it because of God, who called you.
I went back to Jos with the bomb, which I still have with me.
Now, I want to show the whole world the God you serve.
Man of God, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua - please talk to God for me, for the Bible says:
"Confess your sins to one another."
This is the picture of the man.
For security reasons, I think, I will not give you more than that.
This is one out of thousands.
The reason I am showing you this - for you to know the God you are serving.
God wants to reveal to you what He has been doing that you don’t know.
Probably, we may not appreciate what He has been doing.
And I know that because of what I have shown you, those who are faithless may not come here again.
If I had shown it in the past, the faithless generation might have not wanted to come.
It is not only one, two, or three.
I have picked them and I reported them to the security.
Do you know what it means for the church, you trust in so much, to show something on the screen?
You must confirm that it is true.
Because it is not normal to show something which is not true - on the screen.
I was showing it for good two months, still you were saying that it was not true.
Not until you saw their presence somewhere.
What happened – we should believe it so that we can educate our people to be alert.
If not...
I said it last time, concerning Boko Haram, what you are seeing now is not going to stop here,
but our God will get back. Maybe this will be the end of the whole thing.
I want to salute the martyrs, our people who are so faithful to God -
God’s Generals – people who know the God they are serving -
I want to salute them.
Thank you, all over the world.
I want to say,
the story we read for the past three days -
you know, I remained silent - I had to,
because I know...
My life has been like that.
Right from the beginning of my life, people were lying, but they would still come back to the truth.
And that is a good life, for people to lie against you first, before they realize the truth.
If people had realized the truth at the beginning, the story might have not started,
because there is "sorry" all over...
Here I am – I leave you for you to judge.
I am a prophet. Security has a job to do.
Thank you very much.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 30/06/2018 + Mel